[
    {
        "year": "2024",
        "announce": "/snupc2024/",
        "div1contest": "https://www.acmicpc.net/contest/view/1348",
        "div2contest": "https://www.acmicpc.net/contest/view/1349",
        "div1result": "https://www.acmicpc.net/contest/spotboard/1348",
        "div2result": "https://www.acmicpc.net/contest/spotboard/1349",
        "solution": "/assets/pdf/snupc2024solution.pdf",
        "problem": "https://www.acmicpc.net/category/1055"
    },
    {
        "year": "2023",
        "announce": "/snupc2023/",
        "div1contest": "https://www.acmicpc.net/contest/view/1140",
        "div2contest": "https://www.acmicpc.net/contest/view/1141",
        "div1result": "https://www.acmicpc.net/contest/spotboard/1140",
        "div2result": "https://www.acmicpc.net/contest/spotboard/1141",
        "solution": "/assets/pdf/snupc2023solution.pdf",
        "problem": "https://www.acmicpc.net/category/969"
    },
    {
        "year": "2022",
        "announce": "/snupc2022/",
        "div1contest": "https://www.acmicpc.net/contest/view/875",
        "div2contest": "https://www.acmicpc.net/contest/view/876",
        "div1result": "https://www.acmicpc.net/contest/spotboard/875",
        "div2result": "https://www.acmicpc.net/contest/spotboard/876",
        "solution": "/assets/pdf/snupc2022solution.pdf",
        "problem": "https://www.acmicpc.net/category/687"
    },
    {
        "year": "2021",
        "announce": "/snupc2021/",
        "div1contest": "https://www.acmicpc.net/contest/view/691",
        "div2contest": "https://www.acmicpc.net/contest/view/692",
        "div1result": "https://www.acmicpc.net/contest/board/691",
        "div2result": "https://www.acmicpc.net/contest/board/692",
        "solution": "/assets/pdf/snupc2021solution.pdf",
        "problem": "https://www.acmicpc.net/category/686"
    },
    {
        "year": "2020",
        "announce": "/snupc2020/",
        "div1contest": "https://www.acmicpc.net/contest/view/534",
        "div2contest": "https://www.acmicpc.net/contest/view/535",
        "div1result": "https://www.acmicpc.net/contest/spotboard/534",
        "div2result": "https://www.acmicpc.net/contest/spotboard/535",
        "solution": "/assets/pdf/snupc2020solution.pdf",
        "problem": "https://www.acmicpc.net/category/685"
    },
    {
        "year": "2019",
        "announce": "/snupc2019/",
        "div1contest": "https://www.acmicpc.net/contest/view/460",
        "div2contest": "https://www.acmicpc.net/contest/view/461",
        "div1result": "https://www.acmicpc.net/contest/spotboard/460",
        "div2result": "https://www.acmicpc.net/contest/spotboard/461",
        "solution": "/assets/pdf/snupc2019solution.pdf",
        "problem": "https://www.acmicpc.net/category/684"
    },
    {
        "year": "2018",
        "announce": "/snupc2018/",
        "div1contest": "https://www.acmicpc.net/contest/view/335",
        "div2contest": "https://www.acmicpc.net/contest/view/336",
        "div1result": "https://www.acmicpc.net/contest/spotboard/335",
        "div2result": "https://www.acmicpc.net/contest/spotboard/336",
        "solution": "/assets/pdf/snupc2018solution.pdf",
        "problem": "https://www.acmicpc.net/category/683"
    },
    {
        "year": "2017",
        "announce": "/snupc2017/",
        "div1result": "/assets/scoreboard/snupc2017div1/",
        "div2result": "/assets/scoreboard/snupc2017div2/",
        "solution": "/assets/pdf/snupc2017solution.pdf",
        "problem": "https://www.acmicpc.net/category/682"
    },
    {
        "year": "2016",
        "announce": "/snupc2016/",
        "contest": "https://www.acmicpc.net/contest/view/187",
        "result": "https://www.acmicpc.net/contest/spotboard/187",
        "solution": "/assets/pdf/snupc2016solution.pdf",
        "problem": "https://www.acmicpc.net/category/detail/1513"
    },
    {
        "year": "SNUTOC 2015",
        "announce": "/snutoc2015/",
        "result": "/assets/scoreboard/snutoc2015/",
        "problem": "/assets/pdf/snutoc2015problems.pdf"
    },
    {
        "year": "SNUTOC 2014",
        "problem": "https://algospot.com/judge/problem/list/?tag=&source=SNUTOC+2014&author="
    }
]